Ames Family Papers, 1812-2012
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - From SERIES IV: PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Ames, Blanche Ames (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)
      - Photostats, photographs, and galley proof for Adelbert Ames: 1835-1933, Blanche Ames Ames, 1963 (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)
      - Smith College diplomas (2), 1899 (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)
      - Diagrams for excreta disposal system, circa 1967 (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)
    - House plans for Adelbert Ames and Blanche Butler Ames in Tewksbury, Mass., Dec 1906 (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)
    - Bay State Road, Charles River Basin Fill: blueprints, 1931 (Map-case Flat file drawer 28)